{"qid":"easy-dblp-0000","question":"Who are the authors of \"Fluctuations in the Number of Stores by Industry During the COVID-19 Pandemic Based on Japanese Phone Book Entries\"? Seperate the authors with comma and space ', '.","answer":"Saki Saito, Mariko I Ito, Takaaki Ohnishi"}
{"qid":"easy-dblp-0001","question":"Who are the authors of \"Does End-to-End Trained Deep Model Always Perform Better than Non-End-to-End Counterpart?\"? Seperate the authors with comma and space ', '.","answer":"Ikuro Sato, Guoqing Liu, Kohta Ishikawa, Teppei Suzuki, Masayuki Tanaka"}
{"qid":"easy-dblp-0002","question":"Who are the authors of \"Fuzzy Based Association Between China'S Service Industry And Downstream Manufacturing Industry With Liberalization Effects\"? Seperate the authors with comma and space ', '.","answer":"Ling Yang, Linyue Li"}
{"qid":"easy-dblp-0003","question":"Who are the authors of \"On the Performance of RIS-Assisted Integrated Satellite-UAV-Terrestrial Networks With Hardware Impairments and Interference\"? Seperate the authors with comma and space ', '.","answer":"Kefeng Guo, Kang An"}
{"qid":"easy-dblp-0004","question":"Who are the authors of \"Performance Analysis Of Otsu Thresholding For Sign Language Segmentation\"? Seperate the authors with comma and space ', '.","answer":"Zheng Yu Tan, Shafriza Nisha Basah, Haniza Yazid, Muhammad Juhairi Aziz Safar"}
{"qid":"easy-dblp-0005","question":"Who are the authors of \"Hyperparameter Free Mee-Fp Based Localization\"? Seperate the authors with comma and space ', '.","answer":"Rangeet Mitra, Georges Kaddoum, Ghassan Dahman, Gwenael Poitau"}
{"qid":"easy-dblp-0006","question":"Who are the authors of \"A Relative Position Attention Network For Aspect-Based Sentiment Analysis\"? Seperate the authors with comma and space ', '.","answer":"Chao Wu, Qingyu Xiong, Min Gao, Qiude Li, Yang Yu, Kaige Wang"}
{"qid":"easy-dblp-0007","question":"Who are the authors of \"Perfectly Clustering Words are Primitive Positive Elements of the Free Group.\"? Seperate the authors with comma and space ', '.","answer":"MÃ©lodie Lapointe"}
{"qid":"easy-dblp-0008","question":"Who are the authors of \"A modified attention mechanism powered by Bayesian Network for user activity analysis and prediction\"? Seperate the authors with comma and space ', '.","answer":"Alexis Amezaga Hechavarria, M. Omair Shafiq"}
{"qid":"easy-dblp-0009","question":"Who are the authors of \"Wireless monitoring algorithm of intelligent greenhouse based on fuzzy control\"? Seperate the authors with comma and space ', '.","answer":"Xiangling Wang"}
{"qid":"easy-dblp-0010","question":"What organization is Jiezhou He from?","answer":"Hunan Provincial Key Laboratory of Intelligent Computing and Language Information Processing, Hunan Normal University, Changsha, China"}
{"qid":"easy-dblp-0011","question":"What organization is Laura Titolo from?","answer":"National Institute of Aerospace, Hampton, VA, USA"}
{"qid":"easy-dblp-0012","question":"What organization is Foster John T. from?","answer":"Univ Texas Austin, Dept Petr & Geosyst Engn, Austin, TX 78712 USA"}
{"qid":"easy-dblp-0013","question":"What organization is Ni Nie from?","answer":"Megvii"}
{"qid":"easy-dblp-0014","question":"What organization is Joshua J. Levy from?","answer":"Dartmouth Hitchcock Medical Center"}
{"qid":"easy-dblp-0015","question":"What organization is R. Cordero from?","answer":"Univ Fed Mato Grosso do Sul, Fac Engn Architecture & Urban Planning & Geog, BR-79060270 Campo Grande, MS, Brazil"}
{"qid":"easy-dblp-0016","question":"What organization is Maren Hackenberg from?","answer":"Univ Freiburg, Freiburg, Germany"}
{"qid":"easy-dblp-0017","question":"What organization is Damien Rompapas from?","answer":"Extended Real Labs, Brewed Engagement, Adelaide, SA, Australia"}
{"qid":"easy-dblp-0018","question":"What organization is Serdar Tasiran from?","answer":"Amazon Web Services"}
{"qid":"easy-dblp-0019","question":"What organization is Robbert Jan Beun from?","answer":"Univ Utrecht, Utrecht, Netherlands"}
{"qid":"easy-dblp-0020","question":"How many pages is \"Credit financing and channel encroachment: analysis of distribution choice in a dual-channel supply chain\"?","answer":20}
{"qid":"easy-dblp-0021","question":"How many pages is \"5G Early Data Transmission (Rel-16): Security Review and Open Issues\"?","answer":20}
{"qid":"easy-dblp-0022","question":"How many pages is \"Automatic zipper tape defect detection using two-stage multi-scale convolutional networks\"?","answer":17}
{"qid":"easy-dblp-0023","question":"How many pages is \"An image classification approach for hole detection in wireless sensor networks\"?","answer":36}
{"qid":"easy-dblp-0024","question":"How many pages is \"Ddiwas: High-Throughput Electronic Health Record-Based Screening Of Drug-Drug Interactions\"?","answer":10}
{"qid":"easy-dblp-0025","question":"How many pages is \"An Experimental Study to Understand User Experience and Perception Bias Occurred by Fact-checking Messages\"?","answer":12}
{"qid":"easy-dblp-0026","question":"How many pages is \"Network Space Search for Pareto-Efficient Spaces\"?","answer":10}
{"qid":"easy-dblp-0027","question":"How many pages is \"Knowledge Management in Relationship Among Abusive Management, Self-Efficacy, and Corporate Performance Under Artificial Intelligence\"?","answer":26}
{"qid":"easy-dblp-0028","question":"How many pages is \"Modeling System Dynamics of Mixed Traffic With Partial Connected and Automated Vehicles\"?","answer":10}
{"qid":"easy-dblp-0029","question":"How many pages is \"Learning From History: Modeling Temporal Knowledge Graphs With Sequential Copy-Generation Networks\"?","answer":9}
{"qid":"easy-dblp-0030","question":"How many papers in the DBLP citation network cited \"iMag+: An Accurate and Rapidly Deployable Inertial Magneto-Inductive SLAM System\"?","answer":5}
{"qid":"easy-dblp-0031","question":"How many papers in the DBLP citation network cited \"High-Order Approximation Of Heteroclinic Bifurcations In Truncated 2d-Normal Forms For The Generic Cases Of Hopf-Zero And Nonresonant Double Hopf Singularities\"?","answer":5}
{"qid":"easy-dblp-0032","question":"How many papers in the DBLP citation network cited \"Protecting Resources Against Volumetric and Non-volumetric Network Attacks\"?","answer":1}
{"qid":"easy-dblp-0033","question":"How many papers in the DBLP citation network cited \"On the Robustness of CountSketch to Adaptive Inputs.\"?","answer":3}
{"qid":"easy-dblp-0034","question":"How many papers in the DBLP citation network cited \"On Lossy Compression of Directed Graphs\"?","answer":1}
{"qid":"easy-dblp-0035","question":"How many papers in the DBLP citation network cited \"Unanswerable Question Correction In Question Answering Over Personal Knowledge Base\"?","answer":7}
{"qid":"easy-dblp-0036","question":"How many papers in the DBLP citation network cited \"An Upper Confidence Bound for Simultaneous Exploration and Exploitation in Heterogeneous Multi-Robot Systems\"?","answer":7}
{"qid":"easy-dblp-0037","question":"How many papers in the DBLP citation network cited \"The geometry of Bayesian programming.\"?","answer":6}
{"qid":"easy-dblp-0038","question":"How many papers in the DBLP citation network cited \"Smart occupancy detection for road traffic parking using deep extreme learning machine\"?","answer":1}
{"qid":"easy-dblp-0039","question":"How many papers in the DBLP citation network cited \"An Efficient Proactive Secret Sharing Scheme For Cloud Storage\"?","answer":1}
{"qid":"easy-dblp-0040","question":"How many collaborators does Xiaoqiang He have in the DBLP citation network?","answer":4}
{"qid":"easy-dblp-0041","question":"How many collaborators does Roland Roller have in the DBLP citation network?","answer":4}
{"qid":"easy-dblp-0042","question":"How many collaborators does Guy Bresler have in the DBLP citation network?","answer":3}
{"qid":"easy-dblp-0043","question":"How many collaborators does Abdulkadir Sengur have in the DBLP citation network?","answer":7}
{"qid":"easy-dblp-0044","question":"How many collaborators does Songheng Yin have in the DBLP citation network?","answer":2}
{"qid":"easy-dblp-0045","question":"How many collaborators does Guosheng Lin have in the DBLP citation network?","answer":2}
{"qid":"easy-dblp-0046","question":"How many collaborators does Thang N. Dinh have in the DBLP citation network?","answer":5}
{"qid":"easy-dblp-0047","question":"How many collaborators does Chenyi Zhang have in the DBLP citation network?","answer":1}
{"qid":"easy-dblp-0048","question":"How many collaborators does Tom Durrant have in the DBLP citation network?","answer":5}
{"qid":"easy-dblp-0049","question":"How many collaborators does Livia Mannini have in the DBLP citation network?","answer":4}
{"qid":"easy-dblp-0050","question":"How many papers did Rafael A. Calvo and Tuck Wah Leong write together in the DBLP citation network? Papers with the same title are considered the same.","answer":1}
{"qid":"easy-dblp-0051","question":"How many papers did Zifang Huang and Dhruv Jain write together in the DBLP citation network? Papers with the same title are considered the same.","answer":1}
{"qid":"easy-dblp-0052","question":"How many papers did Songling Huang and M. Zhao write together in the DBLP citation network? Papers with the same title are considered the same.","answer":1}
{"qid":"easy-dblp-0053","question":"How many papers did Onur Karaman and Kemal Polat write together in the DBLP citation network? Papers with the same title are considered the same.","answer":3}
{"qid":"easy-dblp-0054","question":"How many papers did Andres Potapczynski and John Cunningham write together in the DBLP citation network? Papers with the same title are considered the same.","answer":1}
{"qid":"easy-dblp-0055","question":"How many papers did Yuanlin Zhang and Yifan Xie write together in the DBLP citation network? Papers with the same title are considered the same.","answer":1}
{"qid":"easy-dblp-0056","question":"How many papers did Tengchan Zeng and Omid Semiari write together in the DBLP citation network? Papers with the same title are considered the same.","answer":1}
{"qid":"easy-dblp-0057","question":"How many papers did Toan-Van Nguyen and Beongku An write together in the DBLP citation network? Papers with the same title are considered the same.","answer":5}
{"qid":"easy-dblp-0058","question":"How many papers did Xianhao Jin and Francisco Servant write together in the DBLP citation network? Papers with the same title are considered the same.","answer":2}
{"qid":"easy-dblp-0059","question":"How many papers did Michael G. Pecht and Remus Teodorescu write together in the DBLP citation network? Papers with the same title are considered the same.","answer":1}
{"qid":"easy-dblp-0060","question":"What papers did Benoit M Dawant write in the DBLP citation network? Seperate the papers with semicolon and space '; '. Papers with the same title are considered the same.","answer":"Atlas-based Segmentation of Intracochlear Anatomy in Metal Artifact Affected CT Images of the Ear with Co-trained Deep Neural Networks"}
{"qid":"easy-dblp-0061","question":"What papers did James Hodson write in the DBLP citation network? Seperate the papers with semicolon and space '; '. Papers with the same title are considered the same.","answer":"Fragile Earth: Accelerating Progress towards Equitable Sustainability"}
{"qid":"easy-dblp-0062","question":"What papers did Felix Portnoy write in the DBLP citation network? Seperate the papers with semicolon and space '; '. Papers with the same title are considered the same.","answer":"How AI Developers Overcome Communication Challenges in a Multidisciplinary Team: A Case Study."}
{"qid":"easy-dblp-0063","question":"What papers did Sai Sagar Jinka write in the DBLP citation network? Seperate the papers with semicolon and space '; '. Papers with the same title are considered the same.","answer":"xCloth: Extracting Template-free Textured 3D Clothes from a Monocular Image"}
{"qid":"easy-dblp-0064","question":"What papers did Liangfei Qiu write in the DBLP citation network? Seperate the papers with semicolon and space '; '. Papers with the same title are considered the same.","answer":"Sponsored Data: Smarter Data Pricing with Incomplete Information; How Learning Effects Influence Knowledge Contribution In Online Q&A Community? A Social Cognitive Perspective"}
{"qid":"easy-dblp-0065","question":"What papers did Rama Syamala Sreepada write in the DBLP citation network? Seperate the papers with semicolon and space '; '. Papers with the same title are considered the same.","answer":"Enhancing long tail item recommendation in collaborative filtering: An econophysics-inspired approach"}
{"qid":"easy-dblp-0066","question":"What papers did Shanley Corvite write in the DBLP citation network? Seperate the papers with semicolon and space '; '. Papers with the same title are considered the same.","answer":"The Online Authenticity Paradox: What Being \"Authentic\" on Social Media Means, and Barriers to Achieving It."}
{"qid":"easy-dblp-0067","question":"What papers did Daniel S Berman write in the DBLP citation network? Seperate the papers with semicolon and space '; '. Papers with the same title are considered the same.","answer":"Handling missing values in machine learning to predict patient-specific risk of adverse cardiac events: Insights from REFINE SPECT registry; Crystal Cube: Forecasting Disruptive Events"}
{"qid":"easy-dblp-0068","question":"What papers did Shidong Zhou write in the DBLP citation network? Seperate the papers with semicolon and space '; '. Papers with the same title are considered the same.","answer":"A 1.6Tb/s Chiplet over XSR-MCM Channels using 113Gb/s PAM-4 Transceiver with Dynamic Receiver-Driven Adaptation of TX-FFE and Programmable Roaming Taps in 5nm CMOS; Guaranteeing QoS for NOMA-Enabled URLLC Based on kappa-mu Shadowed Fading Model; Joint Real-Time Phase Shifter Network Calibration and Beam Tracking for mmWave Communication; Analysis of System Capacity of Grant-free Access with Massive MIMO"}
{"qid":"easy-dblp-0069","question":"What papers did Zhiqiang Li write in the DBLP citation network? Seperate the papers with semicolon and space '; '. Papers with the same title are considered the same.","answer":"An Empirical Study on Heterogeneous Defect Prediction Approaches; Cross-Project Defect Prediction via Landmark Selection-Based Kernelized Discriminant Subspace Alignment"}
{"qid":"easy-dblp-0070","question":"How many papers did Yuheng Deng write in the DBLP citation network? Papers with the same title are considered the same.","answer":1}
{"qid":"easy-dblp-0071","question":"How many papers did Lv Tang write in the DBLP citation network? Papers with the same title are considered the same.","answer":1}
{"qid":"easy-dblp-0072","question":"How many papers did VinÃ­cius Soares write in the DBLP citation network? Papers with the same title are considered the same.","answer":2}
{"qid":"easy-dblp-0073","question":"How many papers did Shuwen Zhang write in the DBLP citation network? Papers with the same title are considered the same.","answer":1}
{"qid":"easy-dblp-0074","question":"How many papers did Andries P. Engelbrecht write in the DBLP citation network? Papers with the same title are considered the same.","answer":1}
{"qid":"easy-dblp-0075","question":"How many papers did Hedda Bakken write in the DBLP citation network? Papers with the same title are considered the same.","answer":1}
{"qid":"easy-dblp-0076","question":"How many papers did Volker Pohl write in the DBLP citation network? Papers with the same title are considered the same.","answer":1}
{"qid":"easy-dblp-0077","question":"How many papers did Deanna M Barch write in the DBLP citation network? Papers with the same title are considered the same.","answer":4}
{"qid":"easy-dblp-0078","question":"How many papers did Dawei Lu write in the DBLP citation network? Papers with the same title are considered the same.","answer":1}
{"qid":"easy-dblp-0079","question":"How many papers did Starchenko Sergei write in the DBLP citation network? Papers with the same title are considered the same.","answer":1}
